{
	"questions" : [
		{
			"id" : 1,
			"question" : "Do a majority of men expect to spend more or less than $50 on a first date?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "60% of men said they expect to spend less than $50 on a first date",
			"option1" : "Spend less than $50 on the first date",
			"option2" : "Spend more than $50 on the first date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 2,
			"question" : "Do a majority of men prefer to pick up their date verses meet their date at a location?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "35% of men prefer to pick up their dates verses 53% of men who would rather meet their dates at a loction. 12% of men prefer to get picked up for their date.",
			"option1" : "Yes. Prefer to pick up their date",
			"option2" : "No. Meet their date at a location"
		},
		{
			"id" : 3,
			"question" : "If a date was not going well, would the average guy go on another date with the same person? ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "Kinda ... 52% of men said they would go up to 2 to 3 dates with a person if the first date didn't go well",
			"option1" : "Yes. Would go on another date with that person",
			"option2" : "No. Would not go on another date with that person"
		},
		{
			"id" : 4,
			"question" : "If a couple could not decide on what restaurant to eat at while on a date, would a majority of men make the final decision or prefer their date to make the final decision?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "62% of men would make the final decision",
			"option1" : "Yes. Make the final decision",
			"option2" : "No. Would like their date to make the final decision "
		},
		{
			"id" : 5,
			"question" : "Do a VAST majority of men like to tell their friends about a date they are going on?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "Actually, only 50% of men would tell their friends about a date. This is different than 85% of women who said they tell their friends about upcoming dates.",
			"option1" : "Yes. A vast majority of men tell their friends",
			"option2" : "No. A vast majority of men do not tell their friends"
		},
		{
			"id" : 6,
			"question" : "If the parents of a guy disapprove of the person they are dating, do you believe that guy will continue dating that person? ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "81% of men would continue to date a person even if their parents disapprove",
			"option1" : "No. Would NOT continue to date that person ",
			"option2" : "Yes. Would continue to date that person"
		},
		{
			"id" : 7,
			"question" : "On a first date, would men rather know if there will be a SECOND date or would men rather know about past relationships?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "55% of men would rather want to know know if there will be a SECOND date, but that leaves a close 45% that would want to know about past relationships",
			"option1" : "Would rather know if there is a SECOND date",
			"option2" : "Would rather know about past relationships"
		},
		{
			"id" : 8,
			"question" : "Do men believe that the check at the end of a date should be split between the two people?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "64% of men believe they should pay for the check",
			"option1" : "Yes men believe the check should be split evenly",
			"option2" : "No men believe they should pay for the check at the end of the date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 9,
			"question" : "If the friends of a guy disapprove of their date, would they continue to see that person?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "88% of men would continue to see a person their friends disapprove of",
			"option1" : "No. They would NOT continue to see that person.",
			"option2" : "Yes. They would continue to see that person."
		},
		{
			"id" : 10,
			"question" : "Do a majority of men consider themselves funny?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "69% of women consider themselves funny",
			"option1" : "Yes. Consider themselves funny",
			"option2" : "No. Do not consider themselves funny"
		},
		{
			"id" : 11,
			"question" : "Do a majority of men play hard to get?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "Only 37% of men play hard to get",
			"option1" : "Yes. Majority play hard to get",
			"option2" : "No. Majority do not play hard to get"
		},
		{
			"id" : 12,
			"question" : "Do you believe the average man likes to become physical on the first date?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "68% of men do NOT like to become physical on the first date",
			"option1" : "Yes. Physical on the first date",
			"option2" : "No. Does not become physical"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Do a VAST majority of men believe they are above average in the bedroom?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "75% of men believe they are above average in the bedroom. Only 50% of women thought the same",
			"option1" : "Yes. Above average in the bedroom",
			"option2" : "No. Not above average in the bedroom"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Do a majority of men consider themselves flirty?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "56% of men consider themselves flirty",
			"option1" : "Yes. Consider themselves flirty",
			"option2" : "No. Do not consider themselves flirty"
		},
		{
			"id" : 11,
			"question" : "Have a majority of men ever made an excuse to leave a date early?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "63% of men said they have NEVER made an excuse to leave a date early",
			"option1" : "No. Never made an excuse to leave a date early",
			"option2" : "Yes. Made an excuse to leave a date early"
		},
		{
			"id" : 12,
			"question" : "When men were asked 'Have you ever dated somebody who was already in a relationship?', what do you believe was the majority of their responses?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "75% said they have dated somebody already in a relationship?",
			"option1" : "Yes. Dated a person who was already in a relationship",
			"option2" : "No. Never dated a person who was already in a relationship"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "If a date lied about their sexual history and was a virgin, would the majority of men be offended??",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "68% of men said they would not be offended.",
			"option1" : "Yes. Offended",
			"option2" : "No. Not offended"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "If a date lied about their sexual history and had many past sexual encounters, would the majority of men be offended?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "62% would not be offended",
			"option1" : "Yes. Offended",
			"option2" : "No. Not offended"
		},
		{
			"id" : 11,
			"question" : "Have a majority of men lied on a date?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "56% of men have lied on a date",
			"option1" : "Yes",
			"option2" : "No"
		},
		{
			"id" : 12,
			"question" : "When men were asked if they thought their date has to dress 'fashionably', what do you believe their response was?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "79% of men responded that dressing 'fashionably' was not important",
			"option1" : "Date needs to dress 'fashionably'",
			"option2" : "Date does not need to dress 'fashionably'"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Would a vast majority of men date somebody 5 years older than themselves?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "Close to 82% of men expressed they would date somebody 5 years older than themselves",
			"option1" : "Yes. Date somebody 5 years older",
			"option2" : "No. Would not date somebody 5 years older"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Would a majority of men date somebody 5 years younger than themselves",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "93% of men said they would not date somebody younger than them by 5 years",
			"option1" : "Yes. Date somebody 5 years younger themselves",
			"option2" : "No. Would not date somebody 5 years younger themselves"
		},
		{
			"id" : 12,
			"question" : "If a date lied about their age and was actually 3 years younger, would the average man be offended?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "82% said they would continue to see that person ",
			"option1" : "No. Would not be offended",
			"option2" : "Yes. Would have been offended"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "If a date lied about their age and was actually 3 years older, would the average man be offended?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "64% said they would continue to see them.",
			"option1" : "Yes. Would be offended",
			"option2" : "No. Would not be offended"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "If a man found out their date was poor, do you believe the average man would want to go another date with that person?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "71% of man said they would go on another date with that person",
			"option1" : "Yes. Would go on another date",
			"option2" : "No. Would not go on another date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 12,
			"question" : "If a man found out their date had no friends, do you believe the average man would want to go on another date with that person?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "61% of men said they would not go another date with that person",
			"option1" : "Yes. The average man would go on another date",
			"option2" : "No. The average man would not go on another date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Would the average man wait 30 minutes for a late date?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "86% said they would wait 30 minutes for a late date",
			"option1" : "Yes. Would wait 30 minutes",
			"option2" : "No. Would not wait 30 minutes"
		},
		{
			"id" : 12,
			"question" : "If the friends of a man expressed their date was not attractive, would the average man continue to go on the date?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "86% of man would continue to go on the date",
			"option1" : "Yes. Continue to go on the date",
			"option2" : "No. Not continue to go on the date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Would a VAST majority of men go dancing on the first date?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "Only 50% of men would go dancing on the first date",
			"option1" : "Yes. Go dancing on the first date",
			"option2" : "No. Would not go dancing on the first date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Would the average man eat dinner with their date's family, as a first date?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "62% of men said they would eat dinner with the family as a first date",
			"option1" : "Yes. First date with the date's family",
			"option2" : "No. No first date with the date's family"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "If a man found a date boring, would the average man would go on another date with that person?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "Only 49% of men would go another date",
			"option1" : "Yes. Go on another date",
			"option2" : "No. Would not go on another date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "If a date did not graduate high school, would the average man consider it a negative or would they not care?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "81% of man would NOT consider it a negative",
			"option1" : "It is a negative",
			"option2" : "It is not a negative"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Would the average man date a friend's ex?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "54% would date a friend's ex",
			"option1" : "Yes. Date a friend's ex",
			"option2" : "No. Would not date a friend's ex"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "If a man embarrassed himself on a date and you laughed at them, would the average man be offended?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "58% of men said they would be offended",
			"option1" : "Yes. Would be offended",
			"option2" : "No. Would not be offended"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Do men prefer to date a person with muscular or non-muscular build?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "65% prefer a date without a muscular build",
			"option1" : "Muscular build",
			"option2" : "Non-muscular build"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Does the average man get nervous before a date?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "81% of men get nervous before a date",
			"option1" : "Yes. Get nervous before a date",
			"option2" : "No. Don't get nervous before a date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "If date smelled bad, would the average man let their date know?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "62% would not tell their date they smell bad",
			"option1" : "Yes. Tell their date",
			"option2" : "No. Would not tell their date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Have a majority of men lied to cancel a date?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "62% of men have lied to cancel a date",
			"option1" : "Yes. Lied to cancel a date",
			"option2" : "No. Never lied to cancel a date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Do you believe an average man needs more than 1 dates to know if they like a person or just 1 date?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "95% of men need more than 1 date.",
			"option1" : "Yes. More than 1 date",
			"option2" : "No. Just 1 date"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "What is more important to men: 'Attraction' or 'Intelligence' ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "53% of men said intelligence is more important",
			"option1" : "Attraction",
			"option2" : "Intelligence"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Would most men date somebody who smokes cigarettes?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "68% of men would not date somebody who smokes cigarettes",
			"option1" : "Yes to somebody who smokes cigarettes",
			"option2" : "No to somebody who smokes cigarettes"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : " What is more important to men: 'Gets along with your family ' vs 'Gets along with your friends' ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "74% of men said getting along with his family is more important",
			"option1" : "Gets along with his family",
			"option2" : "Gets along with his friends"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Do most men consider themselves an above average dater?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "68% of men belive they are above average daters",
			"option1" : "Yes. Above average",
			"option2" : "No. Not above average"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Do most men consider themselves more attractive than the average man? ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "68% of men consider themselves more attractive than the average man.",
			"option1" : "Yes. More attractive",
			"option2" : "No. Less attractive"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "How many people does the average man date at one time?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "79% said just one person at a time",
			"option1" : "2 to 3 people at one time",
			"option2" : "Just one person at a time"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "When men were asked if their last date was arranged online or not online, what do you believe was their response?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "53% percent said their last date was met not online",
			"option1" : "Most said they met their last date online",
			"option2" : "Most said they did NOT meet their date online"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Would the average man be comfortable dating somebody who made 4X the income of himself?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "68% of men said they would be comfortable dating someobody who made 4X their income",
			"option1" : "Yes. Comfortable",
			"option2" : "No. Uncomfortable"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Do you believe the average man would be comfortable taking $100 to go on a date with somebody that repulsed them? ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "63% said they would be uncomfortable",
			"option1" : "Yes. Comfortable",
			"option2" : "No. Uncomfortable"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : " Would a vast majority of men prefer a mate with a 'Sense of humor' over 'Good hygiene'? ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "61% of men prefer a 'Sense of humor' over 'Good hygiene' ",
			"option1" : "Yes. Prefer a 'Sense of humor' over 'Good hygiene' ",
			"option2" : "No. Do not prefer a 'Sense of humor' over 'Good hygiene' "
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : " What is more important to men: 'Their mate's religion' vs 'Their mate's education level' ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "78% believe education level is more important",
			"option1" : "Religion",
			"option2" : "Education level"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : " What is more important to men: 'Being healthy' vs 'Being empathetic' ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "61% belive being healthy is more important",
			"option1" : "Being healthy",
			"option2" : "Being empathetic"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : " What is more attractive to a man: 'Somebody who can stand up for themselves' vs 'Make people around them comfortable' ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "74% find it attractive when their date can make people around them comfortable ",
			"option1" : "Make people around them comfortable",
			"option2" : "Stand up for themselves"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : " What is more important to men: 'The man is sexually attracted to their partner' vs 'Their partner is sexually attracted to the man'? ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "65% of men prefer somebody they are attracted to vs their partner being attracted to them",
			"option1" : "The man is sexually attracted to their partner",
			"option2" : "Their partner is sexually attracted to the man"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Would the average man date somebody with a past drug problem?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "61% said they would not date somebody with a past drug problem",
			"option1" : "Yes. They would date somebody with a past drug problem",
			"option2" : "No. They would not date somebody with a past drug problem"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : " What is more important to men: 'Sexually attractive mate' vs 'A good sense of humor'?  ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "61% of men would prefer a 'Sexually attractive mate'",
			"option1" : "Sexually attractive mate",
			"option2" : "Sense of humor"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : " Which is more attractive: 'Wild in the bedroom' vs 'Sensitive in the bedroom' ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "57% prefer wild in the bedroom",
			"option1" : "Wild in the bedroom",
			"option2" : "Sensitive in the bedroom"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : " Which is more attractive: 'Their date being a good singer' vs 'Their date being a good dancer' ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "52% prefer a good dancer",
			"option1" : "Good singer is more attractive",
			"option2" : "Good dancer is more attractive"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Which of these two would romantically arouse a man more: 'Complimented with sweet words' vs 'A physical caress'? ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "70% said a physical caress would be more romantically arousing",
			"option1" : "Complimented with sweet words",
			"option2" : "A physical caress"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "On average which does a man prefer his partner to have? A higher education degree or a job?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "58% of men said they prefer their partner to have a job",
			"option1" : "Higher education degree",
			"option2" : "A job"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : " Which one of the two options would an average man find more arousing: 'Finger tickling their palm' vs 'A kiss on the cheek' ? ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "67% said a kiss on the cheek",
			"option1" : "Finger tickling their palm",
			"option2" : "A kiss on the cheek"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : "Which do men find more romantic: 'A sweet text' or 'A sweet whisper'? ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "67% said a sweet whisper",
			"option1" : "A sweet text",
			"option2" : "A sweet whisper"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : " Which do more men find more important: 'Their date's religious views' or 'Their date's political views'? ",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "60% said that religious views are more important",
			"option1" : "Religious views are more important",
			"option2" : "Political views are more important"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : " Which do men find more important in a potential partner: 'They smell good' or 'They have good hair'? ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "70% said they prefer their partners to smell good",
			"option1" : "They have good hair",
			"option2" : "They smell good"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Which do men find more romantic: 'They can cook' or 'They are clean' ?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "57% said they are clean",
			"option1" : "They can cook",
			"option2" : "They are clean"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Which do men find more romantic: 'They are sexually open' or 'They are sexually sensitive'?",
			"answer" : 1,
			"answerText" : "73% said they are sexually open",
			"option1" : "They are sexually open",
			"option2" : "They are sexually sensitive"
		},
		{
			"id" : 14,
			"question" : " Which do men find more important in a potential partner: 'They have attractive clothing style' or 'They have a nice body'? ",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "87% said a nice body is more important",
			"option1" : "Attractive clothing style",
			"option2" : "Nice body"
		},
		{
			"id" : 13,
			"question" : "Which do men find more romantic: 'Sensual rub down the chest' or 'Sensual rub on the thigh'?",
			"answer" : 2,
			"answerText" : "57% prefer a sensual rub on the thigh",
			"option1" : "Sensual rub down the chest",
			"option2" : "Sensual rub on the thigh"
		},
	]
}

































